Bjarne Stroustrup created C++ in 1979 when he was only 29 years old.
Bjarne Stroustrup 于 1979 创建 C++  当时他只有 29 岁
He was working at Bell Labs and needed a programming language
他在贝尔实验室工作需要编程语言
to help him maintain clusters of Unix servers.
帮助他维护 Unix 服务器集群
He wanted a programming language with
他想用编程语言
both the high level features of languages like Simula and
无论是 Simula 等语言的高级功能
the raw speed of C. So he created a language that he called C with classes.
他创造了一种他叫 C 的语言
C with classes had features like classes and
C 类具有类和类
also strong types but maintain the lightning fast speed of the C programming language.
也有很强的类型 但保持 C 编程语言的闪电快速速度
C++ as he later renamed it took off and eventually was adopted by
他后来改名为 C++  最终被采纳
the International Standards Organization which created
国际标准化组织
an ISO standard governing the C++ programming language.
用于管理 C++ 编程语言的 ISO 标准
That means that C++ is not controlled by any one person but rather by
也就是说  C++ 不是由任何一个人控制的 而是由
a standards body that meets regularly
一个定期开会的标准机构
to map out the future of the C++ programming language.
勾勒出 C++ 编程语言的未来
In 2011, the C++ Standards Committee
2011   C++ 标准委员会
released C++11 which was a major update to the programming language standard.
已发布 C++11  这是对编程语言标准的主要更新
C++11 turned C++ into
C++11 将 C++ 变成
a truly modern programming language that has both the elegance and ease of
一种既优雅又轻松的现代编程语言
development that we associate with modern programming languages while
我们与现代编程语言的联系
maintaining the raw performance that C++ has always had.
保持 C++ 始终具有的原始性能
Bjarne Stroustrup remains involved in
Bjarne Stroustrup 仍在参与
the C++ programming language to this day as a member of the ISO standards committee,
作为 ISO 标准委员会成员的 C++ 编程语言
and he'll be teaching you throughout this program about
他会在整个节目里教你
the different facilities of the C++ programming language
C++ 编程语言的不同设施